http://amishtraditions.com/index.php/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Who we are
Our website address is http://amishtraditions.com, and we worked on putting together this Privacy Policy so that users have an idea about our practices and content. We also want to disclose the personal information we obtain and how we use it.
Personal Data
We require you to provide your first name, last name, email address, and mobile number when you use our contact form. We also keep tabs of your internet protocol address and visits to the site. We utilize such information for the enhancement of our website and will not be disclosed to third parties unless the law enforcement demands it.
External Links
We have blogs that contain links to external sites. These are third-party websites that are not connected to us in any way. Clicking a link will prompt your server to open a new tab and pull up another site’s page. We cannot guarantee that all the information and practices in the third party’s website are up to your standards. You agree to get redirected to their site when you click the link, and you know that we hold zero responsibility for their policies.
Contact Form
We have a contact form in place to initiate a conversation between the users and us. You may fill it up with your data (as mentioned above) and message. You can expect a reply to come to the email address that you have provided.
Changes
This Privacy Policy may get modified whenever there is a brand-new service offered by this site.
We do not send notifications when we make changes. It is advisable to visit this Privacy Policy page from time to time to understand the new policies or practices.
